Improved By: Fidel33
Sub Upload Date: December 17, 2015
(FILM PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CREAKING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(FILM PROJECTOR RUNNING)
(EXHALES)
(WHISPERS) Hey.
This is the part where you say,
"Bless me, Father, for I have sinned."
Yes.
How long since your last confession?
(CLEARS THROAT)
I've, actually, uh...
I've never had a confession before.
You've never had the
Sacrament of Reconciliation?
No, I've never had any sacraments
that I can think of,
not that I can remember.
I mean, I may have had one by accident.
To tell you the truth, I
actually never even been
inside of one of these, or
like a church or anything,
but there was a funeral... I'm sorry.
(SIGHS)
I didn't know who else to talk to.
You're the deputy from that Oswalt thing.
Well... I'm not on the force anymore.
But you are him, right?
Yeah.
So...
if I... if I tell you something,
it stays between us, right, like lawyers?
Yeah, but I'm gonna ask
you not to tell me anything
that I can't unhear,
if you know what I mean.
Okay.
Do you believe in evil?
I mean, of course you do, you know.
You mean, do I believe in the supernatural?
Ghosts and demons,
and the devil himself.
Something like that, yeah.
This is about your friend, your case.
What did you find?
I don't know, I can't explain it.
It's something, uh...
otherworldly.
And you want to know how to stop it.
Yes.
What do you want me to say?
You should carry a cross and holy water,
and shout, "The power
of Christ compels you?"
Why, would that work?
- No.
- (SCOFFS)
Right.
- You want my professional advice?
- Yes.
You don't stop evil.
You can only protect yourself from it.
Do I believe things that
you're talking about exist?
Yes.
And I believe they exist to
lure men like you into them.
Stay out of it, whatever it is.
(SIGHS)
Whatever happened to the Oswalts
is only gonna happen again.
It's a question of when and where.
(WHIRRING)
- Gotcha!
- (IMITATES GUN FIRING)
- What?
- You didn't make the noise. You didn't say the words.
- No, I killed you.
- I shot you in the back.
- You're hit. I got you!
- Uh-uh.
No, I got you, I killed you!
You did not make the noise.
Boys. Boys!
Did you guys take those
out of their packages?
No. They were in a bin like this.
You're putting 'em back.
(BOY LAUGHS)
Pick out your cereal.
(BOYS CHATTERING)
Dude, these are so much
better than yours.
Yeah, but these are healthy.
You're supposed to pick sugar,
that's the whole point of cereal.
No, no. One box each.
- They all look so good.
- BOTH: Can we get two each?
No.
You boys stay close, okay?
BOY: Okay.
What is it, Mom?
You boys remember what to do
when Mama says "rutabaga", right?
BOTH: We run.
Yeah, and stay close together.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Rutabaga.
Rutabaga!
- WOMAN: Oh, my God!
- GUARD: Hey, hey!
Wait, wait a minute. Slow down!
- Dylan!
- What's wrong?
That man back there just
touched one of my boys.
Hey, son. You need to step back.
What'd she tell you?
(KEYS JINGLING)
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- Seatbelts.
BOTH: Yeah.
(TYRES SQUEALS)
(HORN HONKS)
Yeah, it's her, all right.
ZACH: Race you inside.
What?
Dylan?
You okay?
What is it?
Okay, well, I think I'm gonna
go finish up work for a bit.
You think you can make
dinner with your brother?
Okay.
Hey.
You did good today.
DEPUTY: Yeah, hi, I'm calling
about the Jacobs property.
Yeah, I'm looking at the listing.
Uh, is it still available?
Oh, it is.
Okay. No, that's great.
My clients are gonna be
very, very happy about that.
Yes, they, um... they
are aware of the incident.
Yeah, their only question is
has anyone lived on
the property since then?
No one.
It's been vacant for that long?
Okay. No, no, I'll, um...
I'll let them know.
Okay, thanks.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLANKING)
(LOUDER CLANKING)
(KNOCKING)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Mom.
Yeah, sweetie?
- Dinner.
- Okay.
I'll be... I'll be there in a minute.
Dylan?
You okay, baby? What's wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, Dylan. It's just
an old building, baby.
I know.
- (SIGHS)
- (CLANKING)
ZACH: How long
are we gonna be out here?
(WHISPERS)
Not long. I promise.
I'm worried about Dylan.
Why?
He's just...
different out here.
Yeah, well...
he'll come around. He will.
But he's gonna need a
little help from his brother.
Do you think you're up for it?
(SIGHS)
Good.
'Cause I really can't do this alone.
I need my boys.
Good night.
Sweet dreams.
- Hi, Milo.
- Hi, Dylan.
What are you doing here?
I have something to show you.
I'm supposed to be asleep.
Your mom just started working.
She'll be out there for hours.
What if she comes back?
She won't.
- How do you know?
- I just know.
(SCOFFS)
Do you trust me?
What's down there?
You'll see.
It's back there.
(CLICKING)
Come on.
(CLICKS)
Should I open it?
What's on them?
There's only one way to find out.
How'd you know this was here?
This is where I left it.
(MACHINE WHIRS)
(HAUNTING MUSIC)
Hey, Ted. What are you doing here?
Milo said he was gonna
show you the thing.
This one's mine.
(PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
(ROARING)
We shouldn't be watching this.
Turn it off, Milo. Let's get...
BOTH: Shh.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WIND RUSTLING STALKS)
- (TOY SQUEAKING)
- What the hell?
(TOY SQUEAKS)
Uh...
Mom!
- Hey!
- Whoa, hold on, ma'am.
No, no, no. This is private property.
Wait, wait, wait! No, I was
told the house was for sale.
The listing said it was available.
Doesn't give you a right to be out here.
You're trespassing and you know
it. What are you doing here?
I'm a private investigator.
- (WHISPERS) Oh, you son of a bitch.
- What?
- How the fuck did you find me?
- Hold on, what?
Was that your partner back
there at the grocery store?
Partner? No, I work alone.
You listen to me, okay?
You listen to me.
- Okay.
- You are not taking them.
He is not taking them,
do you understand me?
- Okay.
- I don't care who his friends are.
- Okay?
- Okay, yeah.
Good, okay.
(PANTING)
Okay, you look like a reasonable man.
You do. Are you a reasonable man?
Um...
I mean, yeah, I guess.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
What's it gonna take?
I mean...
(STAMMERS)
What is he paying you?
I don't have a lot, but I...
I will pay you what I have
to make sure that
you never saw us, okay?
So just tell me what it's gonna take.
Coffee.
Excuse me?
A cup of coffee. It's
been a really long trip,
and I think that there has
been a huge misunderstanding.
Um... have you ever heard
of someone named Ellison Oswalt?
Yeah. Yeah, who hasn't heard about that.
That was terrible what happened.
Mr. Oswalt was a friend of mine.
I was helping him on his
book that he was writing
- about the case...
- Oh, so...
Are you here 'cause of
what happened at the church?
Yes, ma'am.
You think they're related?
No, they...
The crimes share a lot of similarities.
I'm just following up on
cold cases that look similar.
Hmm. How's there any money in that?
There's not, really.
But fortunately,
there's always somebody
that needs a private detective
to check in on a spouse or an employee,
- so when I'm not doing that...
- You do this.
Yeah.
Uh...
Have you ever seen
anything on your property
that looks like this?
No.
Mmm. You weren't supposed to be here.
I was told that this place was empty.
Right. My friend Jillian,
her dad owns the land now,
and when things between my
husband and I went south,
she was nice enough to put us up here,
but she told me that
nobody ever comes out here.
Oh, so... So the boys, is that...
Do you have legal custody, or is that...
I do, yes. It's, uh...
It's temporary, though.
Well, look, you...
You're welcome to stay
awhile and look around,
- whatever you need.
- No, it's getting late.
You don't want to creep around
a murder scene in the dark, huh?
No, ma'am.
In all honesty, I do not.
- It's Courtney.
- Okay, Courtney.
Do you mind if
I come back here tomorrow
and have a look around?
No, but on one condition.
- Anything.
- Nobody gets to know that we're here.
No one.
I don't know who I'd tell.
Good.
Goddamn it. Damn it!
Karen! Karen?
COURTNEY: Boys, let's, uh...
Let's get ready for bed.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Brush your teeth.
Can we just watch till the next commercial?
- No, now.
- ZACH: Come on!
I don't like it when you boys
watch stuff like that before bed, okay?
It's not real, Mom. It's
okay if it's not real.
Yeah, but it'll still give you nightmares.
So let's go, come on.
Brush your teeth.
What did that man want today?
- Uh...
- Was he one of Daddy's friends?
No, no, no. He was just
looking for something.
DYLAN: Was he here about
what happened in the church?
What do you mean what
happened in the church?
We know about the church, Mom.
We're not stupid.
Hey, who told you two about
what happened in the church?
We just heard about it.
Yeah, everyone knows.
All right, well, I don't want you two
thinking about that, okay?
Dylan? Is that why you're
afraid of the church, baby?
You don't have to worry about that, okay?
There's nothing in that
church that can hurt you.
Hey! Hey, you guys.
- (MAKES CHOKING NOISE)
- Hey, hey, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, come on.
Brush your teeth, let's go.
(ZACH WHISPERS)
What happened in the church?
(SIGHS)
What?
What the...
(WHISPERS) What...
What?
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Come on. Let's watch another.
No, I don't want to watch any more of them.
(PANTING)
Hi, Emma.
Are you having the dreams?
We all had the dreams.
The movies make the dreams go away.
Once you watch them all,
you never have a bad dream again.
For real?
Swear.
Let's watch another.
No. I don't wanna
watch any more movies.
But you have to.
You haven't watched the best ones yet.
Besides, you won't have
any more bad dreams tonight.
Or tomorrow if you watch another.
Good night, Milo.
You aren't so special, you know.
- What?
- I can see them too.
You aren't so special.
Aren't you gonna say anything?
Hey, answer me. Pussy.
Zachary Collins, what did
you just call your brother?
- Nothing.
- Don't you tell me "nothing".
Okay, remember what I told you boys?
BOTH: Speak only
when spoken to,
and tell you what he asks us.
So here it is.
The scene of the crime.
So how were they killed?
Do you know?
Unfortunately, I do.
Tell me.
Trust me, you don't want to know.
Uh...
I'm gonna look around in
here for a few minutes.
I'm gonna compare the space to
some of the crime scene photos.
Yeah, sure. Uh, please.
Come back to the house
if you have any questions.
I will.
Thanks.
(WHISPERS) Okay.
(CLANKING)
(CLATTERING)
(KNOCKING)
(RAPID KNOCKING)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
(SQUEAKING)
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
(EXHALES)
Oh.
(SIGHS)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
(FLOOR CREAKING)
(COUGHING)
Come on.
(GRUNTING)
What?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (RINGTONE SOUNDS)
- Oh!
Hello?
- Deputy?
- Well, I'm not really on the force anymore.
No, right. Of course, I'm sorry.
Who is this?
I'm Dr. Stromberg.
We spoke a few months back.
You're like, the new
Professor Jonas or something?
God, I hope not.
Jonas is missing.
STROMBERG: The police
just called off the search.
(COUGHS)
Well, what happened to him?
Look, I need you to, uh...
to come out here as
soon as possible.
Uh, I'm a little tied up
with something right now.
Look, Jonas left...
he left something behind.
Something unbelievable.
I think it could be
the key to all of this.
Then tell me.
No. No, no, no.
I can't... I can't risk that.
- Not on the phone.
- Okay.
- I'll be there tomorrow.
- Yeah, okay, that's good.
Great, thank you.
(SQUEAKING)
DEPUTY: Hey.
Dylan, right?
How do you like it out here?
Be better if I didn't live
where so many people got killed.
So how you dealing with that?
(SIGHS) I get it.
(SCOFFS)
I'd be scared too.
And I'd have nightmares
in a place like this.
You having nightmares?
Yeah.
Yeah, I have really bad
dreams too sometimes.
About dead people?
A friend.
What do you do?
To stop the dreams.
Well, when I'm awake,
I try to help people.
You know, make the real world
a little less like the dreams.
You let me know
if the dreams start to feel
a little too real, you know?
I'm pretty good at
dealing with nightmares.
(CAR APPROACHING)
Oh, no.
You cut your hair.
Bastard.
COURTNEY: How dare you
show up here?
(ANOTHER CAR APPROACHING)
What the fuck is this?
I told you this would happen.
Told you I'd come for 'em.
No, no, this is bullshit.
You don't have a court order.
- You can't do this.
- Step aside, ma'am.
You need a court order.
Boys, get back in the house!
- Step aside.
- Get back.
- Ma'am...
- No, you can't do this!
- You need to step...
- Let's see the order.
Step aside, sir. Now.
Who's the officer in charge?
I'm in charge, asshole.
Okay, okay, Officer...
Shermer. Where's the sheriff?
We're state troopers.
We don't have a sheriff.
- Now if you could...
- I know, I know. I can read the car.
I know that you're state troopers.
But I also know that
child custody transfers
is the responsibility of the sheriff.
And I can tell you from experience
that the only reasons that
the sheriff isn't here today
is because he either
doesn't know about it,
or he doesn't want to know.
So, you want to call him?
You know what?
I'll call, I got it.
Don't worry about it.
Sir, put the phone away
or I'm gonna throw you
in the back of the car myself.
Are you saying that you'd arrest me?
In a heartbeat.
Well, then I should probably inform you
that I was arrested a few years
ago on a big capital offense.
It was a major news story.
All the charges were dropped.
But if I were to be arrested again,
that'd be pretty big news. Yeah.
Whew! If the press got a hold of it...
Ugh. I would hate to be the uniform
that was trying to make a child abduction
look like a custody transfer.
State cars and everything?
That just might be the
worst day of that guy's life.
Sir.
(LAUGHS)
- Let's go.
- Gary? Hey.
I'm not leaving without my boys.
Look, that douche canoe
over there is right.
We don't have any legal
authority to be here.
He called our bluff.
I'm sorry, I can't lose my job over this.
I got kids too.
- This isn't over.
- (ENGINES STARTING)
Whore.
- Thank you.
- (EXHALES HEAVILY)
Thank you so much for doing that.
It's, uh... it's really no problem.
We gotta get outta here.
What? No, no... No.
- No, no, you, um...
- What?
You can't leave.
- Why?
- Uh, did you, um...
Did you have a restraining order?
No. No.
He had too many character witnesses.
I was lucky I got custody.
You have to stay because those officers
can testify that they saw you here today,
and if you leave overnight, then...
he will have a case that
you're a flight risk.
(SIGHS)
And he could get the boys.
Yeah. Yeah, he could.
But you saw him.
(SIGHS)
He'll come back.
Will you stay?
(STAMMERS)
Maybe just... for dinner?
Sure.
Sorry, I, uh...
They're used to...
Clint always ate first.
Well, I'm not Clint, so go ahead, eat.
(CHUCKLES)
So, were you a cop or something?
Oh, yeah.
A sheriff's deputy.
So you saw dead bodies and stuff?
- Zachary.
- What?
Cops see dead bodies.
That's okay. Um... Yeah, I did.
More than I'd like.
- Did you catch...
- Did you catch a lot of bad guys?
Uh, not bad guys. Just people.
Having bad days.
ZACHARY:
But you're not a cop anymore.
- No.
- Why not?
(SIGHS) Uh...
Because I got tired of seeing
people on their bad days.
I think you're good at dealing with people
on their bad days.
Thanks.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Uh, thanks. Thanks for dinner.
You don't have to leave.
No, I... I have a really
long drive in the morning,
and it's... it's dark.
Does this place really
spook you that much?
No, it's not like that.
Yes, it really does.
It's really no problem.
I can fix up the couch.
- No...
- DYLAN: Please stay.
(LAUGHS)
(SHATTERING)
Oh, shi...
(SIGHS)
What the hell am I doing here?
Jesus Christ.
You can't sleep, huh?
(LAUGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
No.
- (GLASS CLINKS)
- DEPUTY: Do you smoke?
Uh... no.
Not really, um... This
is a secret cigarette,
- 'cause I'm a secret smoker.
- Gotcha.
You can't say anything to my boys.
They don't know.
Okay, sure. I don't know when I would.
I'm not their dad. That's weird.
- That is weird.
- (BOTH LAUGHS)
Don't say that.
It's like, oh, well, I wish you were.
(LAUGHS)
Was that true today what you said earlier,
about getting arrested?
Yeah. It's true.
You didn't do it... did you?
No, no. God, no. No,
it's nothing like that.
(CLEARS THROAT)
That writer I was telling
you about, Ellison Oswalt.
He's a friend of mine.
I gave him some files
and some information,
even after my boss told me not to.
And since I was the last
person to talk to him,
and the only other person
they saw coming and going
from his home,
I was a really easy suspect.
I was cleared of all the charges.
Your boss was pissed 'cause
you went behind his back.
Yeah. Yeah.
Fired me the day that I was cleared.
- (SIGHS)
- You miss it, huh?
Most days.
- Yeah, I do.
- Mmm.
(SIGHS)
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Ask away.
Was it Dylan?
What do you mean?
That he hit.
(SIGHS)
How could you tell?
It's just that he reminds me of me.
Clint beat him real bad.
He sent him to the emergency room.
All his cop buddies
weren't gonna do anything.
So you left.
Yeah.
So what's the plan?
Uh... get the hell out of here.
(BOTH CHUCKLES)
Know where you're gonna go?
Far as I can.
What are you gonna do?
Get a job, I guess.
- Yeah, furniture stuff?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I saw inside the church.
- It's really cool.
- Thank you.
It's antique restoration, actually.
It feels almost magical
to turn something worn out
into something that's...
something that's beautiful
again, you know?
Like, polished and worthwhile.
Something that's gonna be
here long after you're gone.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Like kids.
Yeah, like kids.
Come on.
I don't want to.
I want to go back to sleep.
Sweet dreams.
(SIGHS)
This one's mine.
Just play it.
(CLICKING)
I know you're there.
Why'd you have to pick him?
Because you're not good
enough to be one of us.
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
You're not smart enough
to do what he can do.
Uh-uh. I'm better than
him. I'm smarter too.
If you were, then we would
have chosen you.
Tell anyone of this,
and he'll take you first,
then kill your whole family.
Who, Dylan?
Then who?
- (MUTTERING)
- Okay. Okay.
- (BOTH WHISPERING)
- Okay, okay.
Ooh!
- I can...
- Shh.
Now, listen up. Listen up.
- I live alone, so...
- Shh. Okay.
My God, I have to go to bed.
(LAUGHING)
I have to go to sleep.
Okay.
It's been so long since I felt safe.
Sorry.
No, don't... it's not sorry.
I, um... I need to go to bed.
Yeah. Yeah, tomorrow...
I have... Um... I have a long...
- I have a long drive tomorrow.
- Okay, okay.
Are you gonna be okay?
- Yeah. Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Okay.
Okay, good night, Courtney.
Good night.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Hey!
Oh, hey.
Got you this for the road.
You didn't have to do that.
Really. Thanks.
(CHUCKLES) You're going to
have to bring that back, though.
Oh, I promise. I'll be back tomorrow.
But... But listen.
Whatever you do, don't...
don't leave the house. Okay?
Trust me.
Okay.
Okay. All right, and I
left my number inside.
Yeah, I got it. That's mine.
So call me when you get there safe
and if you need anything.
Yeah, okay. Um, same deal.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
- Okay.
- I'll see ya.
- See ya.
"Same deal"?
Same deal.
Jesus.
Sorry. Uh, thanks.
DEPUTY: Oh, yeah, sure, man.
Uh, so, uh...
- (OBJECT CLATTERS)
- I'm not really sure...
- You all right?
- Yeah, no, I'm fine.
Uh, just a little too much coffee.
Um, you wanna take a seat?
Yeah, sure. Thanks.
Great. Um, here, uh...
Look, I really appreciate
you making the trip.
You're helping me.
Yeah.
You want a drink?
No, that's okay.
I'm going to have a drink. Cheers.
Um... what is all of this about?
(SIGHS)
Um...
have you ever seen one of these?
This? Yeah, sure, it's a ham radio.
Oh, great, then you've heard
of the Norwegian bughuul.
No.
Um...
years ago,
back in the '70s,
several ham radio enthusiasts,
they ran across a strange transmission.
One night, out of nowhere,
on a rarely used band,
this... this children's piano
starts tinkling.
And for years... I
mean, this thing would...
it would come and go...
I mean, it became an urban legend
until one day,
in the late '90s...
someone finally caught it on tape.
(TOY PIANO PLAYING)
CHILD: Eight, nine, nine...
five, zero, zero...
one, zero, seven...
five, one, nine...
Stop.
(SPEAKING NORWEGIAN)
(SCREAMING)
(PIANO CONTINUES)
W-What were the numbers?
- Coordinates.
- To where?
A house. A farm.
In the middle of Norway, where
an entire family was murdered...
in 1973.
So tell me, this murder...
is there a...
Missing child?
(CHILD SPEAKING NORWEGIAN)
bughuul...
- (CLICKS COMPUTER)
- bughuul...
Bughuul.
Are there other broadcasts like this?
There are at least three others like it.
Now, this radio I have seen
over with Jonas' things,
along with this map.
But Jonas found the pattern.
Yet the families are only
murdered after they leave the house
where Bughuul found them.
That's how I've been stopping it.
I've been burning the houses down.
Wait, so the Oswalt house?
That was...
Yeah.
The pattern isn't the only
thing that Jonas found.
He also realized the piano
was of particular significance.
There are fragments... references...
to Bughuul... the Bogeyman...
across all cultures, over
the centuries, that...
some cultures believed
that it lived in another realm,
reachable only by ritual
or sacrifice.
And others believed that it... it fed
off of the corruption of innocents,
but no matter what,
there are always three things in common.
There's a murdered family,
missing children,
and some form of iconological totem
or a thematic offering.
An image, literature, music.
Okay, so the murders
are captured through art?
It's aesthetic observance of violence.
But that little girl,
the piano,
what exactly did she say?
It's Norwegian.
She says...
"Quiet, Bughuul can't hear
me over your yelling, Mom."
It's the kids.
He gets the kids?
(STATIC CRACKLING)
DEPUTY: (OVER RADIO)
It's the kids.
DR. STROMBERG: (OVER RADIO)
He gets the kids?
DEPUTY: (OVER RADIO)
It's the kids... kids...
(CRACKLES)
Okay, you should probably
destroy that thing,
like soon.
Yeah, yeah, I really should.
Listen to me.
There's another problem.
I found another house.
Then burn it down.
Break the chain again.
I can't. It's not that simple.
There's already a family
that's living in there...
a mother and her two...
and her two boys.
Jeez... What... Detective!
(GRUNTS)
Say it!
- Stop it!
- Say it!
Say I'm better than you!
Say it!
Say it! Say it! Say it!
Okay, okay.
You're better than me.
- (GROANS)
- Say you're nothing.
Say you're weak.
Say they made a mistake.
I hate you. I hate all of you.
I'm telling Mom.
You hear that? I'm telling Mom.
Shh.
You don't deserve that.
You should do something about him.
And your father.
And your mother.
My mother didn't do anything.
Exactly.
COURTNEY: Damn it, Zachary!
What were you thinking?
- ZACH: But Mom!
- "But Mom" what?
Give me one good reason, one good reason,
why it was okay for
you to hit your brother?
Never mind. I'm sorry. Okay?
Okay, you t... you tell
that to your brother.
Fuck you, Dylan!
Fuck you too.
Cunt.
What, are you going to
hit me now? Like Dad?
Go to your room...
and do not take a single step out
until I say so.
I didn't do anything, Mom.
I know, sweetie.
Just weak.
You are not weak.
Don't you ever say that
about yourself. Okay?
You're strong.
Okay? You're like me that way.
Zachary, he's just, um...
Like Dad?
No, I didn't mean that.
But it's true, and you know it.
Dylan, I'm never going
to let anybody hurt you.
You let him.
And you let Dad.
(CRACKS)
(LOUD HIT)
(DOOR RATTLING)
(MUSIC)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMS)
(REPEATING, PROJECTOR SKIPPING)
(GASPS)
You're going to like this one.
It's my favorite.
No. I don't want it. Not today.
It has to be tonight.
If we don't do this tonight, then...
Then what?
He'll get real mad at us.
You don't want to make him mad.
Please, Dylan. This one's mine.
I made it.
(MUSIC)
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(MUSIC STOPS)
This is the last one.
No. No more.
Just... on... more.
No.
TOGETHER: Yes!
It's downstairs, Dylan.
Last chance to watch
the last movie, Dylan.
No, Mylo.
I won't watch any more movies.
I don't want to be like you.
That's fine.
They weren't really
meant for you anyway.
What?
You did what we needed you to do.
(FILM PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
Zach. Zach.
Zach.
Zach!
Go to bed, Dylan.
Tell anyone,
and we'll kill you and your whole family
and watch the film over and over and over.
(LOUD WHIRRING CONTINUES)
(PROJECTOR STOPS)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
What the hell does this say?
There was an emergency
hearing last night.
Sorry you couldn't be there.
Judge T. Simmons. Tory
Simmons' boys work for you.
Well, you'd be hard-pressed to
find anybody within five counties
that doesn't have a
family that works for me.
This isn't right.
This isn't legal.
Oh, you want to ask the sheriff?
Don't...
let the kids see you in cuffs.
You're not taking my boys.
Our boys.
I'm just taking them where they belong.
You're welcome to come
with me if you like.
Fuck you.
Either you can stay here
without the boys,
fighting the courts for custody
until you run out on money,
or you can come home with me,
spend all the time in the world with them,
making cute little tables and chairs.
Either way, I'm taking them.
Dylan, I need you to pack
your stuff quickly, okay?
Honey, the police are downstairs,
and if you don't come out on your own,
then they're going to come up here.
Mom, I can't go.
We have to, baby. We have to go.
You don't understand.
You don't know what's going to happen.
Nothing's going to happen.
He's going to hurt us.
I don't like this any more than you do.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm going to take care of us.
Now, get your stuff.
Okay?
Come on.
No.
(MUTTERING) Fuck.
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Smells good.
Come on. Come on.
Pass the mashed potatoes.
Thank you, son.
You haven't touched your food.
I'm not very hungry.
Come on, buddy.
I got a big day planned for us tomorrow.
You're going to need all that energy.
Eat!
Clint! Stop that now!
(BANGS TABLE)
(CHUCKLES)
Boys have to eat.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
Mr. Collins, I know that it's late
but... but I need to speak...
You need to speak with me?
Or my wife?
What? No.
No, it's not... it's not like that.
- You don't understand...
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
I understand.
Once you get a piece
of a woman like that,
it's hard to shake it off.
Okay, you are in danger.
I'm in danger?
Okay, just listen.
I'm in danger? Huh?
Listen.
- I'm trying to...
- Say it again!
I'm in danger?
Say it again!
Now...
if you ever try to contact my wife again,
first I'm going to take it out on her hide.
And then I'm going to come and find you,
and I'm going to shoot you.
Am I making myself
perfectly fucking clear?
Now, get off my property
while I go fuck my wife.
All right, just stand up straight.
Keep your eyes on the
ball. All right? Ready?
COURTNEY: Oh, good, baby.
CLINT: Come on.
Sure they're gonna like this one.
CLINT: Ready?
Go for it. Hit the ball.
Jesus, why are your hands like this?
- (PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
- (NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(ENGINE REVVING)
- (SQUEAKS)
- (THUDS)
(GROANING)
I'm gonna make the best one yet.
CLINT: Zach?
Is that you? Zach?
Zach! Zach!
(SCREAMING)
CLINT & DYLAN:
Zach! Zach...
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(SCREAMING)
(COURTNEY SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(DISTANT SCREAMING)
Oh, God.
(CRASHES)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Okay, listen. It's me. I'm here.
Just hold still. All right?
It's okay. I'm going to get you down.
- (GROANS)
- I'm gonna get you down.
Okay. It's okay.
It's okay. I got you.
I got you.
Okay. Give me your hand.
It's okay. Dylan.
(PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
Hold still.
Okay. You all right?
- Huh?
- Baby.
You better finish this, Zach.
Zach!
- No, run! Now!
- Zach!
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Okay.
Oh!
- It's okay. Hurry.
- I'll tie it. Hold it.
- Oh, God!
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
Wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Wait.
They're here somewhere, Zach.
It's time to find them
and finish your movie.
(PROJECTOR RESUMES)
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
We gotta get in here. Come on.
Quick.
Shh.
In here.
(PROJECTOR WHIRRING)
(NOT AUDIBLE)
(BOOKS CRASHING)
(GROANS)
Run! Courtney!
(GHOSTLY WHISPERING)
(CRASHING)
DEPUTY: Hey!
(MUTTERING) No, no.
It's over, Zach.
You're not making them a film.
No. No, no, no!
No! No!
No!
Please be another camera.
Oh!
He's going to be mad.
He's going to be so mad.
It's over.
You can never come back.
No, I'm not finished!
It's too late.
You had to kill them all.
Zach? Zach!
- DEPUTY: He's gone!
- (COURTNEY SCREAMS)
No, no, no, Courtney. He's gone.
We have to go.
Courtney, we have to go.
Go! Now! Go! Go!
(SOBBING)
I got her.
I love you, Mom.
Be right back.
(CRACKLING)
MALE VOICE:
The kids. It's the kid... kids.
CHILDREN: It's the kids.
He gets the kids.
It's the kids. He gets the kids.
CHILD: Deputy.
Deputy.
(RADIO CRACKLING)
(TOY PIANO PLAYING)
(STOPS)
Improved By: Fidel33
Sub Upload Date: December 17, 2015